Matthew C. Armstrong

074571 48856

Flat 21 Hitherwood Court, 28 Charcot Road, London, NW9 5YW mcarmstrong@mail.com

Resume

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To attain a position within a modern organisation that will enable me to utilise and further develop my years of experience within the Technology and IT fields. I am comfortable in high pressure and deadline driven environments, adept at identifying and solving problems while communicating solutions to end users and customers while working with management to solve ongoing issues.

KEY SKILLS	
Desktop Support	Network Engineering and Infrastructure
1 st & 2 nd Line I.T. Support	Systems Administration
Office 365 Experience	Excellent Customer Service
Basic HTML and CSS	Management Experience
CERTIFICATIONS / ACCREDIDATIONS	
(CCENT) - Cisco Certified Entry Networking	Technician Valid through April 202
Verification Number 435694169757ERAF	

EXPERIENCE

Training Period

January 2019 - Present

• Left previous position to enhance my technical abilities by pursuing a number of technical certifications and self-study courses in subjects including Cisco Networking, Office 365, Citrix Workspace, and VMWare virtualization. Achieved CCENT certification in April 2019.

Utility Warehouse / Telecom Plus: Technical Support Advisor

November 2017 - June 2018

Promoted to: Technical Operations Analyst

June 2018 - January 2019

- Hired to answer calls from residential and business customers, providing expertise to resolve technical equipment, setup, and operational faults for home phone, broadband, and mobile phones.
- Resolved problems ranging from equipment and customer premises wiring, infrastructure faults, wireless difficulties, as well as advising on a wide range of operational and software issues.
- Provided excellent customer service and ensured customer satisfaction and resolution; escalated any complaints through proper channels to supervisors.
- Promoted to 2nd line Operations after 8 months to address faults raised by first line support via investigating the issue in further detail and managing resolutions within the established SLA.
- Resolved over 800 individual faults in 2nd line operations ranging from infrastructure failures, core network misconfigurations, equipment and setup issues, as well as wireless networking problems.
- Utilized, and became proficient with concepts of ISP infrastructure, network architecture, Wireless LAN principles, mobile phone networks, VoIP, telephony and ITIL model helpdesk Support.
- Investigated the nature of customer issues and provided relevant support and resolutions through the use of Openreach Strategic Indicatives, TalkTalk Business, and EE's Strategic Partner Website with their respective API's.
- Generated activity reports for all customer contact, including raising support tickets for faults, maintaining open tickets through Zendesk, ordering equipment, direct account commands, billing and payments, and general correspondence.
- Exceeded expected call quality, calls per hour, and customer satisfaction metrics throughout my employment period in both roles. Regularly received monthly bonuses due to performance.
- Assisted in training of new hires in both roles via call shadowing and advisement.

Matthew C. Armstrong

074571 48856

Flat 21 Hitherwood Court, 28 Charcot Road, London, NW9 5YW mcarmstrong@mail.com

Personal Growth Period

January 2015 - October 2017

- After growing personal savings for 8 years, left previous employer to pursue personal goals.
- Successfully budgeted for and accomplished a lifelong goal of travelling the world: Europe, Africa, Asia 34 countries over the span of two and a half years.
- Improved my sense of self confidence, initiative, communication, and problem solving skills.

The Fender Music Foundation: Tech Support Specialist

October 2012 - December 2014

- Administered and maintained all office computers and peripherals for the foundation, including Windows and Apple systems, file and print servers, printers, faxes, and software licenses.
- Reported to Fenders' corporate I.T. department on issues such as Microsoft Exchange, hosting of the foundations website, and foundation access to corporate information on company file servers.
- Managed and administered the entire foundation inventory of thousands of musical instruments and equipment through a system of tracking numbers and spreadsheets.
- Administered the foundations' off-site e-commerce and inventory store, hosted by 3dCart. Was liaison to 3dCart for all technical and operational issues.
- Participated in an extensive inventory audit of the foundations finances and item donations throughout its history through research of all past donations, item valuations, and grants.
- Tripled the foundations social media engagement through Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram.
- Reported monthly results on social media engagement and communications while analyzing performance, pinpointing trends and new ways to creatively market the foundation.

Self Employment: Technology Consultant and Computer Repair March 2010 – October 2012

- Promoted, and marketed tech services for hire through Facebook, Instagram, and Craigslist.
- Repaired and performed initial set-up services, as well as virus and malware removal for Windows, Apple, and Linux systems.
- Performed repairs, installations, and custom firmware flashing of both Apple and Android devices.
- Handled all customer enquiries, complaints, billing questions, and payment plan requests.
- Counseled clients on perspective equipment purchases based on analysis of their personal or professional requirements.
- Supervised the installation of client systems, networks, and peripherals.

Target Corporation: Photo Lab Specialist

June 2008 – February 2010

- Managed a team of three, and supervised all department operations such as organizing shift rosters; supply and chemical orders; and maintained department systems and equipment.
- Processed all customer orders and invoices, handled online orders for later customer pick-up.
- Worked with contract technicians from Kodak to ensure product quality, suggested product upgrades to improve customer satisfaction.
- Directly maintained all photo department machines and equipment, including handling processing chemicals, optical systems, customer kiosks, and dye-sublimation printers.
- Used customer satisfaction survey information to identify focus areas for improvement. (Note: Department was first in customer satisfaction in the district of nine stores for all of my tenure.)

EDUCATION

Napa High School

2002 - 2006

Napa, California, USA

Pierce College: Associates Program in Computers and Networking

2011 - 2012

Los Angeles, California, USA

References available upon request.